Hello.
In this next lecture, we're going to go over how we can design and create a nice 2D level.
To get started, I want us to briefly close Unreal Engine and attached.
In this course lecture, I'm going to include this free, cute tile set.
Make sure to download it and drag it somewhere inside of your Unreal Engine project.
Once you've done that right click and go sprite actions and apply paper to detect your settings on all
of the images.
We're going to create a new level.
So if we go file and then go new level and select basic and then go create, then save this and cool
this level one Make sure to save this in our level folder, just to keep everything organized.
So let's level one and then go save.
And I'm just going to go add and go basic and add a player start.
And I'll make sure we're in the two D game mode.
So under K mode, let's select two D game mode and make sure our two D character spawns in this level.
Okay, Nice.
The next thing we're going to do is create a background for our level.
There are two ways to do this.
The first way is to find an image of a background that you only use in your game.
So something like background one would work.
And once you find the image, just right click and go spread actions and then go create Sprite.
Okay, so my sprite turned green.
I'm not sure why this happens, but sometimes when we create a sprite, if it's blue, it can sometimes
be green.
In order to fix this, if we go over to the original image and could do compression settings and just
change this to be default and then go save.
And that should fix it.
Once you've done that, dragging your sprite and position it behind our player character.
And I'm just going to scale this up a bit.
So let's make it 30.
And I'll move it a bit further back.
And now about go play.
We kind of have this background for our two D game.
In the next video, I'm going to show you another way that we can create backgrounds for two D games.